well gentlemen what's happening what's happening what's happening
bueno señores qué pasa qué pasa qué pasa
lately the disasters are
que últimamente los desastres están
ending in a very strange way
terminando de una forma muy rara
a very strange way I don't know what's
una forma muy rara no sé lo que está
going on I do
pasando
n't know if you remember but a few months ago I do
no sé si acordaréis pero hace unos meses
n't remember exactly how many she had a
no me acuerdo exactamente cuántos tuvo
thing there with a guy who uploaded
una movida allí con un chico que subió
a clip of hers a video not talking about
un clip suyos un vídeo no hablando de
her about her relationship
ella de su relación con el fbi y se
with the fbi and it got really heated she got really heated with the guy I don't want to even imagine I don't want to even imagine the survey that you're doing I can read it I can read it I don't know if you remember if I don't forget to leave it in the description if I
olvida lo dejar en la descripción si se
forget to leave it the description
me olvida dejarlo la descripción poner
you put the comments I will leave it at the end
ustedes los comentarios yo dejaré final
with the comment they are worth it in the excerpt
con el comentario valen en el extracto
but but basically it was with a
pero pero básicamente fue con un
very big heat with the guy and in the
calentón muy grande con el chaval y al
end we were watching it
final lo estuvimos viendo tampoco dijo
the guy didn't say anything bad or offensive or
el chaval algo malísimo ni ofensivo ni
anything and it turns out that well apparently he has
nada y resulta ser que bueno que por lo
responded to her again let's
visto ha vuelto a responderle vamos a
see it a
verlo
while ago she made a video in which aro
hace tiempo hizo un vídeo en el cual aro
jeep commented saying threats like he was
jeep comentó diciendo amenazas como que
going to take down my channel and continue to take down the
iba a tirar mi canal y seguir a tirar
channel and embargo that he was going to
del canal y embargo que iba a
report him but he
denunciarlo pero nuevamente volvió a
responded again  editing the comment and today I'm
responder editando el comentario y hoy
going to respond to that it's
voy a responder a eso
back in time and there it is the
ha vuelto al tiempo y allí está el
comment I've been
comentario he estado
gracia rodríguez I don't know why it doesn't come out
gracia rodríguez no sé por qué no sale
of your comment tired of the harassment I
de tu comentario cansado del acoso que
received simply because of the whim of
recibí simplemente por el capricho de
arroyito
arroyito
hundreds of people commenting
cientos de personas comentando
insulting me calling me everything even
insultando llamándome de todo incluso
going to my instagram in which I
yéndome a mi instagram en el cual
simply upload drawings to insult me
simplemente subo dibujos para insultarme
and the truth is that I'm quite because she didn't
y la verdad que estoy bastante porque no
like a video she wanted to express it in a
le gusto un vídeo quiso expresarlo en un
live and thousands of followers went to
directo y miles de seguidores fueron a
throw hits at me
tirarme hits
so I'm going to show you all the
entonces les voy a mostrar todas las
lies idiocies that she says in her new
mentiras idioteces que dice en su nuevo
comment she starts by saying I edit
comentario ella empieza diciendo edito
this because she doesn't care already
esto porque ella me da igual ya
starting memos the stupidity of the
iniciando memos la estupidez del
comment since if there is something the same you don't
comentario ya que si algo tiene igual no
look for the video and look among
buscas el vídeo y buscas entre
comments for your comment to edit it
comentarios tu comentario para editarlo
and respond again to look for the
y volver a responder para buscar el
comment either because when you
comentario tampoco porque cuando tú lo
do it from your channel the first comment does
haces de tu canal el primer comentario
n't appear in the video of yours I'll give you
no te sale en el vídeo del tuyo te daré
an example it's like you're walking down the
un ejemplo es como que vayas por la
street and in quotes you see two people
calle y entre comillas ve a dos personas
criticizing you funny site ekiza
criticándote sitio de gracia ekiza
thank you very much you would probably ignore
muchísimas gracias igual pasarías de
them I wouldn't respond to them but  yes time is well I would
ellos no les respondería pero sí tiempo
answer things that you
está pues les respondería cosas que tú
just did and then he says changing
acabas de hacer y luego dice el cambiar
the thumbnail
la miniatura
where it showed me with sacks of money and
donde me ponía con sacos de dinero y
wings with a broken heart reinforces
alas con el corazón roto refuerzan más
my theories that I was slandering
mi teorías de que estaba difamando en
instead of entertaining well because in that way I
vez de entretener bueno porque tal forma
was insinuating that she was
estaba insinuando como que ella estaba
with him for interest
con él por el interés
and that in truth she didn't feel anything for it she
y que en verdad no sentía nada por ello
was using him something like that no I
lo estaba utilizando algo así no yo me
imagine that she would feel offended because she would
imagino que se sentiría ofendida porque
understand it that way another proof that she doesn't care
lo entendería así otra prueba de que no
since to make a theory
le da igual ya que para hacer una teoría
observations are required like in your
se requiere observaciones como en tu
life in which it goes wild is talking about
vida en el cual se desboca esté hablando
informing you without even knowing
de que te informe sin ni siquiera saber
the definition of information then
la definición de la información entonces
watch out for this changing the thumbnail where you
ojo a esto el cambiar la miniatura donde
showed me with sacks of money already to them with a
me ponías con sacos de dinero ya les con
broken heart reinforces mommy theories
el corazón roto refuerza mami teorías de
that I was slandering instead of
que estaba difamando en vez de
entertaining watch out for this it says with sacks of
entretener ojo a esto dice con sacos de
money and to him with a broken heart and
dinero y al es con el corazón roto y
here I am going to show you the thumbnail jac
aquí le voy a mostrar la miniatura jac
but a person so big let's see
pero una persona tan grande a ver
not that enormous area but he has
tampoco esa enorme área pero tiene
many viewers now he has many
muchos espectadores ahora tiene muchos
followers and so on he becomes so obsessed
seguidores y demás se obsesiona tanto
with a video I mean  more than the video
con un vídeo o sea por más que el vídeo
bothers you because well because it can
le moleste porque bueno porque le puede
bother you it is your right to be
molestar está en su derecho de que le
bothered otherwise no
moleste demás no
but to such a point of realizing if you
pero a tal punto de ir darse cuenta si
change the thumbnail you do not give too much
cambia la miniatura no le da demasiada
importance to this video that I still
importancia a este vídeo que aún la
have it and so that you see that it is not false and
tengo y para que vean que no es falso y
that simply in its montage I am going to
que simplemente en su montaje le voy a
show you the date of the details of the
mostrar la fecha de los detalles de la
photo at what time the old island and the one I
foto a qué hora la isla vieja y la que
currently have as you can see the
tengo actualmente como pueden ver la
thumbnail that I changed was made on
miniatura que cambié fue hecha el 22 de
January 22, 2021,
enero del 2021
Friday at 2:21 and the one I
viernes a las 2 y 21 y la que tengo
currently have was made on January 22,
actualmente fue hecha el 22 de enero de
2021, Friday at 3:28 made
2021 el viernes a la 3 y 28 hecha
simply an hour later since I
simplemente una hora después ya que
changed the thumbnail not because I have
cambie la miniatura no porque la haya
defamed it I am criticizing it simply
difamado le esté criticando simplemente
for aesthetic reasons since because if you
por motivos estéticas ya que porque si
see they only change aesthetic themes, I
ven solo cambian temas estéticos a un
leave the letters and the only thing I removed
dejo las letras y lo único que retire
was the bag of money,
fue la bolsita de dinero
the nonsense even leaving the same
la tontería dejando incluso la misma
photo only removing the galaxy from the
foto sólo que retirándole la galaxia de
background now I don't know if you noticed that he did not
fondo ahora bien no sé si notaron que ni
even close the parenthesis that also
siquiera cerró el paréntesis que también
talks about his spelling but he wants to
habla de su ortografía pero se quiere
hold on to the  little bag of money
aferrar de la bolsita de dinero
simply as if it is already defamation
simplemente como que ya es difamación
again making you remember what it
otra vez haciéndole recordar lo que
means of information information
significa de información de información
is negative information that is said in
es información negativa que se dice en
public or written about a person
público o se escribe de una persona en
against their good name their fame and their
contra de su buen nombre su fama y su
honor especially when it is false
honor especialmente cuando es falsa a
based on this you are telling me that the
base de esto me estás diciendo que la
little bag of money this information or
bolsita del dinero esta información o
rather I also put it in the video but it
sea también la pongo en el vídeo pero
only matters to you because I changed the
solamente te importa porque cambie de
thumbnail and I no longer put it after that I
miniatura y ya no la puse después
also put it in the video
igualmente la pongo en el vídeo
precisely also when she explained that you do
justamente también cuando explicó de que
not do it for the money so you
no lo haces por dinero así que no te
can not hold on to that simply eye I do not say
puedes aferrar a eso simplemente ojo no
Carolyn simply goes back the
digo carolyn simplemente va atrás el
simple money just when in the video
dinero simple justo cuando en el vídeo
when I also put it clarified second
cuando también la pongo aclaró segundo
after that you are not going to waste the money
después de que no vas traste el dinero
then she says the videos yes I can
luego dice los vídeos sí que puedo
delete them because it is content that
borrarlos porque es contenido que
directly belongs to me and I can
directamente me pertenece y puedo
do it without any problem you cannot you
hacerlo sin ningún problema
cannot the legitimate use that I have
no puedes no puedes el uso legítimo que
spoken everything with whoever I have to
lo he hablado todo con quien tengo que
talk to I do not love it I love the way
hablar no me encanta me encanta la forma
of saying I have spoken everything with whoever I
de decir lo he hablado todo con quién
have to talk to knows how
con quien tengo que hablar lo sabe como
the plan is careful in taking care of develops and I
el plan cuidado en cuidar desarrolla y
have a team of three years which
tengo un equipo de tres años cosa que
shows that if there is a video or something that is
demuestra que si hay un vídeo o algo que
not  they like it just take advantage of the fact that she
no les guste simplemente aprovecha que
has an audience that supports her to
tiene un público que la apoya para
criticize her and her audience will give her a hand
criticarlo y su público le dará la mano
you can throw out a video because she has
puedes tirar un vídeo porque se ha
contained your reason although she is
contenido tuyo la razón aunque está
wrong and why because they
equivocada y por qué porque simplemente
are simply children children that when I
son niños niños que cuando yo les
respond to them they comment doing all kinds
responda lo comenta haciéndome todo tipo
of things asking for proof and arguments they do not
de cosas pidiéndole pruebas y argumentos
even respond to me because they do not
ni siquiera me responden porque no
have the proof or the arguments
tienen ni las pruebas ni los argumentos
nor do you have it to say that
ni tú tampoco lo tienes para decir que
I defame you or criticize you and when in
yo te difame o te critique y cuando en
my videos
mis vídeos
I have deceived someone I have only
yo he engañado a alguien solamente he
told the truth here the only one who
dicho la verdad aquí la única que se
is deceiving herself is yourself and then she says I have
está engañando es tú misma y luego dice
spoken with youtube and if they have not
he hablado con youtube y si aún no han
deleted anything yet neither in this channel nor in
borrado nada ni en este canal ni en
any other it is because I am busy with a thousand things
ningún otro es porque ando con mil cosas
and I am lazy to put all the videos of
y me da pereza poner todos los vídeos de
this type because they have asked me
este tipo porque me han pedido
what is wrong with the link here we see the
qué les pasa el link aquí vemos la
truth another stupidity you cannot do is
verdad otra estupidez no puedes hacer es
that if you start sending the line to
que si te pones a mandarle la línea a
send to eliminate channels to begin with we
mandar que eliminen canales para empezar
are going to criticize you all okay we are going to
te vamos a criticar todos vale te vamos
criticize you all and second
a criticar todos y segundo
[Music]
[Música]
lion since how are you that the time
león ya que tal como estas que el tiempo
that has spent us here
que nos ha pasado por aquí
a huge kiss  and thank you so much
un besote enorme y muchísimas gracias
for those beats apart from the fact that we're
por esos beats aparte de que la vamos a
all going to criticize it because the
criticar todo el mundo porque eso la
truth was terrible you
verdad estaba fatal
have to take down a channel because
hay que tirar un canal porque te molesta
a video bothers you, I mean maybe take down the video
un vídeo o sea a lo mejor tirar el vídeo
still but take down the channel itself he
todavía pero tirar el canal en sí me
's threatening to take down the channel but the thing is that
está amenazando con tirar el canal pero
in such a way I wouldn't recover by
es que de tal manera no recuperaría
appealing I would recover it doing a thousand things
apelando lo recuperaría hacer mil cosas
and then you get lazy to do something
y que luego te dé pereza hacer una cosa
as simple as sending the link of this
tan simple como enviar el link de este
channel to YouTube then he says because
canal a youtube luego dice porque a
unlike Perez to send some lists
diferencia a pérez a mandar unas listas
of others I have a busy life yes of course you have
de otros tengo una vida ocupada sí claro
such a busy life that you went back to
tienes una vida tan ocupada que volviste
look for this video you search through
a buscar este vídeo rebuscan te entre
the comments and you edited it again
los comentarios y volviste a editarlo
what a busy life and then he says that I
qué vida tan ocupado y luego dice que
said things in the heat of the moment that I think is
dije cosas en caliente que creo que es
an incorrect way of expressing yourself
una manera incorrecta de expresarse
because I'm tired of channels like yours
porque estoy cansada de canales como tú
that want to profit from things by speaking
que quieren lucrarse a cosas de hablar
badly of others sorry and again here I
mal de otros perdón y otra vez aquí le
tell you that I never spoke badly of Arroyito I did
digo que nunca hablé mal de arroyito yo
not speak negatively about Harghita at
no hable negativamente de harghita en
any time nor did I say anything that
ningún momento ni tampoco dije nada que
was especially false because doing that
sea especialmente falso porque que hagan
for visits is fine since when you
eso por visitas está bien ya que cuando
work on a content platform
trabajas en una plataforma de contenido
public your job is
público su trabajo es
visit then you can't offend
visita después no puedes ofender
saying there is that he told me that I do it
diciendo ahí es que me dijo que lo hago
for visits when your job is to gain
por visitas cuando tu trabajo es ganar
visits and of course you can talk about
visitas y claro tú puedes hablar de todo
everyone talking about profiting about
el mundo hablando de lucrarse acerca de
someone else when it is totally what
alguien más cuando es totalmente lo que
you have done in your entire career since
tú has hecho en toda tu carrera ya que
if we analyze your statistics from the
si analizamos tus estadísticas desde el
moment you thought about role play it
momento en que pensaste en role play
increased considerably when
aumentó considerablemente cuando
you started to get together with farc then it
comenzaste juntarte con farc luego
increased even more when you started to
aumentó aún más cuando empezase a
get together with bg it is among others like
juntarte con bg está entre otras como
willy to xxvi etcetera and if you don't believe me I
willy al xxvi etcétera y si no me creen
give you a smart me you have to look at the
les doy un smart me hay que mirar a la
graph it was like he crashes before that the me I believe
gráfica era como él choca antes de eso
even worse if it is that look look at
yo creo incluso peor si es que mirad
the store I
mirad el store
wrote that this
escribí that esto
wow
guau
example and here are those of minguito
ejemplo y aquí están las de minguito
another character even more loved than
otro personaje incluso más querido que
her in role play in which she herself
ella en roll play en el cual ella misma
was also but that never got together
estaba también pero que nunca se juntó
with what I had already mentioned see the
con lo que ya había mencionado ven la
difference but of course here it is not bad to
diferencia pero claro acá no está mal
profit from other people it is not
lucrarse con otras personas no es
basically the same case in which two
básicamente el mismo caso en el cual dos
people started with a
personas se iniciaron con una cantidad
low number of visits when they got together
de visitas bajas cuando se juntaron
confagán increased the difference is that
confagán aumentaron la diferencia es que
you  started then you finish the oak
tú comenzase luego que terminas el roble
then to get together with the others vegetal we
pues a juntarte con los demás vegetal we
live argan to xxvi and since this girl
live argán al xxvi y como esta chica
managed to meet with those people gave to a
consiguió darse con esa gente dio a una
girl who was not popular I think I'm
chica que no era popular creo que a
exaggerating but I think it's normal for her to get
rollito exagero pero creo que es normal
angry if you graphically insinuate that
que se enoje si insinúa gráficamente que
money is a factor in their relationship
el dinero es un factor en su relación
totally totally clear that moment you
totalmente totalmente claro ese momento
crash thank you thank you
el chocas
and thank you Rodriguez let's
gracias gracias y gracias rodríguez a
see it's totally understandable that it
ver es totalmente entendible que le
offends her and that she is upset by the fact that she
ofenda y que se moleste el hecho de que
says that of course their relationship is only
diga que claro de su relación solamente
because of the visit because of the fame and so on
por la visita por las famas y demás no
but of course
pero claro
when the public figure at the end of the day
cuando el personaje público al fin y al
is exposed to the crime of you
cabo está expuesto al crimen de ti
not to the point that they can get into your
no al punto que se puedan meter en tu
private life either although it depends a
vida privada tampoco aunque depende un
little I know them well all
poco de lo conozco los conozco bien todo
the content of haro and no I don't know
el contenido de haro y no no conozco
well if she has made more
bien si ella ha hecho vídeos más
personal videos talking about her life or
personales hablando sobre su vida o
only makes video games I don't
solamente hace videojuegos no lo
ignore it okay but when you are a
desconozco vale pero cuando tú eres un
public figure you are
personaje público
more you have like more
eres más tienes como más
there is more right for the public to have an opinion
hay más derecho al público a que opine
about you about what you do on the internet
sobre ti sobre lo que haces en internet
also that they get into your private life they
tampoco que se metan en tu vida privada
bring out very personal things are missing  with
saquen cosas muy personales falten al
respect okay but for example if you
respeto vale pero por ejemplo si tú
talk about your relationship or things like that
hablas de tu relación o cosas por el
on the internet in your videos and you make
estilo en internet en tus vídeos y gana
money from it
dinero con ello
then people who I'm not saying is the
luego la gente que no digo que sea el
case of halogen karime thank you very much
caso de halógeno karime muchas gracias
for giving them a cookie subscription I
por regalarles a suscripción a cookie me
imagine it will be our cookie no
imagino que será nuestro cookie no
thanks jaime
gracias jaime
then I don't know if it's the case of
entonces desconozco si es el caso de
haro already from choirs and in his case he
haro ya de coros y en su caso
has talked a lot about his private life in
ha hablado mucho de su vida privada en
videos and so on okay but if that were the
vídeos y demás vale pero si fuera el
case then he has to understand it if you
caso pues tiene que entenderlo sí que de
really want if it hasn't been ugly
verdad queréis si no ha sido de fea
javi even mangel already confirmed the
javi hasta mangel ya confirmó la
relationship between those two and well yes I think
relación de esos dos y bueno sí yo creo
they themselves are not hiding
que ellos mismos ya no se ocultan no
themselves like that even the blonde
ellos mismos así incluso el rubio lo
said it
dijo
even the blonde said something like
incluso el rubio dijo algo así como a
but did you have any doubts that they were a
pero tenías alguna duda de que eran
couple I don't know what something like that the blonde said I
pareja no sé qué algo así dijo el rubio
don't remember but we saw it here but the
no me acuerdo pero lo vimos aquí pero la
thing is one thing that you think about their relationship and
cosa una cosa que opine de su relación y
another thing that we did that I'm
otra cosa que hicimos
not saying is illegal to say it or
que no digo que sea ilegal decirlo ni ni
defamation either like she is saying
difamación tampoco como está diciendo
but hey if you do public relations
ella pero oye si tú relaciones públicas
and have
y tiene
a relationship with another streamer for each
una relación con otro streamer por cada
one can have their opinion on what they want  Hey, well,
uno puede opinar lo que quiera oye pues
I think that she started hanging out with
yo opino que ella se empezó a untar con
him because he was famous. Well, I don't
él porque él era famoso bueno yo tampoco
see anything wrong with her
le veo nada malo
getting close to him or his acquaintances
acercado a él o los conocidos
because something caught your attention and
porque te llamaba la atención algo y
then in the end, well, you're in love with
luego al final pues estás enamorado de
him and you liked him or whatever. I don't know, I
él y te ha gustado o lo que sea no sé te
understand what you're saying is wrong, you know, but I do
entiendo que decir está mal sabe pero
n't see him as a dad either. Why is that so much the
tampoco lo veo como papá papá para tanto
point? If you're going to focus on him, he's right. But I also think it must be
razón pero creo que también debe ser
annoying that they want to pass off an opinion as
molesto que quieran pasar una opinión
fact. Yes, but what does it matter what
como un hecho sí pero que importa lo que
a guy with 40 views says, let's be literal,
diga un tío con 40 visitas sea literal
not to belittle him, but this guy
no por menospreciar pero este chico
with 129 views
tiene 129 visitas
is giving her more hype than she
le está dando a ella más bombo que el
would have had if she didn't get any
que hubiera tenido si no lograra un
hype, it
bombo
's not absurd.
no es absurdo
[Music]
[Música]
Minguito, I understand the annoyance, I
minguito que entiendo la molestia que
understand the annoyance because, listen, your
entiendo la molestia porque oye tu
job, your relationship, is in a
trabajo en tu pareja está en un momento
very sweet moment, he's very much in love with whatever
muy dulce está muy enamorado a lo que
and there are people saying, you're getting close,
sea y hay gente diciendo estás acercaba
really, no, because what is happening is what
en verdad no porque lo que está lo que
the guy in the video was a little bit hard to understand.
se lo quedaba un poco a entender el
Thank you very much. What
muchísimas gracias lo que daba un poco a
the guy was implying in his video was that
entender el chico en su vídeo era que
she  the truth is that she didn't like
ella en verdad que a ella no le gustaba
the one who was with him simply for the
el que estaba con él simplemente por el
money he carries the bag of money because
dinero lleva el saquito de dinero pues
if you notice she emphasizes a lot about the
si os dais cuenta ella recalca mucho del
bag of money it's like what
saquito de dinero es como lo que le
bothered her not the fact no to the fact that you're only with
molestó no el hecho no al que sólo estás
him for the money
por el por el dinero
damn why is she upset well if you're
ostia porque está molesta pues si estás
insinuating no about my life now well it
insinuando no sobre mi vida ahora bien
also depends a lot on the ways okay
depende mucho también las formas vale
or so well I can say that Levy
o sea pues yo puedo opinar que a levy
is much more done chao with her than
está mucho más hecho chao con ella que
rolled at least that's what they
arrollado por lo menos eso lo que
pretend in public hey but
aparentan de cara al público oye pero la
more in his private life it turns out that it's the
más en su vida privada resulta que es al
other way around hey well I think that Aro already
revés oye pues yo opino que aro ya se
approached him to get together with him for
acercó a juntarse con él por temas
work issues because he was more interested in
laborales porque le interesaba más
collaborating with him so that he would do better
colaborar con él para que le fuera mejor
at work okay in fact he has done
en su trabajo vale de hecho él ha ido
better when he gets together with them and after
mejor cuando se junta con ellos y a raíz
knowing him he has fallen in love it depends
de conocerlo pues ha enamorado depende
a lot on the way that people are free to have an
mucho la forma que la gente es libre de
opinion what they want you
opinar lo que quieras
know as long as they express it they
sabes siempre que cuando lo exprese lo
do it without disrespect while
haga sin faltar al respeto mientras que
that person will not disrespect
esa persona no te hará falta el respeto
you I understand his annoyance sincerely
a ti entiendo su molestia sinceramente
no  I'm going to tell you that he didn't remember us
no os voy a decir que no nos recordaba
at first yes if you see this treatment and at
al principio sí si veis este trato y al
first
principio le quita un poco de
the guy downplays the video a bit because he didn't
importancia al vídeo el chico porque no
remember that
recordaba como tal
part as such man Victor what a joy I didn't
esa parte hombre víctor qué alegría no
know you were tweets what a joy
sabía que estabas tweets qué alegría
Victor a huge hug man thank you so much
víctor un abrazo enorme tío muchísimas
for that radio requeté thanks
gracias por esa radio requeté gracias
man I send you a huge hug Victoria
tío te mando un abrazo enorme victoria
another one who has hair that looks like a
otro que tiene el pelo que parece un
white toothbrush fluorescent blue
blanco azul fosforito
but he's a lovely kid if you like
pero es un encanto de chaval si os gusta
sports the world of football and so on he's
el deporte el mundo del fútbol y demás
a crack he's a crack
es un crack es un crack
not until now around here you can know that
no hasta ahora por aquí podés saber que
I am the most rounded thing I've seen in my
yo soy lo más redondo que visto en mi
life it was a brick a brick that
vida fue un ladrillo un ladrillo que se
fell off the fence of ai of my building
cayó de la valla de ai de mi edificio
but well I appreciate it very much seen
pero bueno yo lo aprecio mucho al visto
very good people and he has been supporting me
muy buena gente y me ha estado apoyando
on many occasions when I needed it
en muchas ocasiones cuando lo necesitaba
so thank you very much Victor a
así que muchísimas gracias víctor un
big kiss that is that I understand
besazo que eso es que entiendo
perfectly that the girl bothers him she
perfectamente que la chica le moleste
is telling us that she is that you are with
nos está diciendo que está que estás con
the guys simply for fame but I don't
los tíos simplemente por la fama pero no
understand her annoyance okay I understand her
entiendo su molestia vale entiendo su
annoyance but perhaps
molestia pero quizás
without realizing it so that you can see how
sin darse cuenta para que veáis como
many times  thinking in your head
muchas veces el pensar en caliente te
makes you make bad decisions and many
hace tomar decisiones erróneas y muchas
times the best thing if you know how to stay
veces lo mejor si sabes mantenerte en
cool I'm faced with I used to act a lot in your
frío estoy ante actuaba mucho en
head but over time I've learned a
caliente pero con el tiempo he aprendido
way to mature it has been to
a una forma de madurar ha sido el
meditate and know not just for the sake of it it's
meditar y el saber no porque sí que
true that before I used to act a lot in your
verdad que antes actuaba mucho en
head I was very impulsive and such no in
caliente era muy impulsivo y tal no de
fact I still follow it a little because
hecho lo sigo siguiendo un poco porque
my nature is not but when you go
mi naturaleza no pero cuando tú vas
and think things through better well look
y piensan mejor las cosas pues mira tal
maybe instead of giving
vez ella en vez de haberle dado bola a
this guy the ball put a comment like if I'm
este chico ponerle comentario que si te
going to throw the channel at you that if I don't know that I don't
voy a tirar el canal que si no sé que no
know how much well I had told him hey look
sé cuánto pues le había dicho oye mira
sorry an email a dm an email an email
perdona un email un md un email un email
so as not to draw attention they don't bring themselves to
para no llamar la atención no se traen a
know each other to see in some debate my side comes out
saberse a ver en algún debate me sale el
see be but it depends on the case there is no
lado ver ser pero depende el caso no
reason I have to have a girlfriend and
tiene tengo que tener motivo novia y
people screaming in my face as
chillando la gente por la [__] cara como
if I were from here the exorcist line
si fuera de aquí la línea de exorcista
the thing is that she would have sent him an
la cosa es que ella lo hubiera mandar un
email I would have said hey look kid you've
email le hubiera dicho oye mira chico te
gone too far here I think you've gone too far
has pasado aquí creo que te has pasado
because with the one you're implying
porque con el que estás dando a entender
this and if you realize and put yourself in my
esto y si te das cuenta y te pones en mi
place this  it is very ugly
lugar esto es muy feo
or not that is why the difference in the number
o no por eso la diferencia de cantidad
of followers on twitter / minguito and you
de seguidores en twitter / minguito y tú
but I am not saying that it is wrong that you would join
pero no digo que esté mal que te juntará
with these people obviously not because
con estas personas obviamente no porque
making visits is your job and if you
hacer visitas es tu trabajo y si te
like those people and if they
agradan esas personas y si ellos lo
accept it and try it even better but
aceptan y lo prueban mejor aún pero
when you have been profiting by joining
cuando tú te ha estado lucrando juntando
you with people who have a much greater
te con personas que tienen mucho mayor
number of subscribers and followers and
cantidad de suscriptores y seguidores y
another thing to add is that my content
otra cosa añadir es que mi contenido no
was not directed to controversy or
iba dirigido a polémicas ni a de
information or criticism before the
información ni a críticas antes del
video of haro x which she took it
vídeo de haro x el cual ella se lo tomó
badly because prior to that new one to
mal pues anterior a ese nueva a que
fix they fixed she has not achieved with fact
fijar fijaron no ha conseguido con hecho
look at Ávila the visits that
mirar ávila las visitas que tiene ese
video has and look what she had before
vídeo y mira lo que tenía antes
in no criticism video she
en ningún vídeo de crítica solamente
would have only made a video titled the
hubiera hecho un vídeo titulado la
truth about blonds in which she talked
verdad sobre rubios en el cual hablaba
about the criticism that came to her about
sobre las críticas que le llegaban sobre
her decision division says valeria
su decisión división dice valeria
was part of mac lion before and
formaba parte de mac lion desde antes y
was also friends with henry who is from the
también era amiga de henry que es el del
vegeta group and was also known
grupo de vegeta y también era conocida
maximo and he invited her to play with them
máximo y él le invitó a jugar con ellos
supporting neither is to say as that she has been
apoyando tampoco es decir como que ha
looking for her, that
ido buscándola
is, she herself said in an interview
o sea ella misma dijo en una entrevista
of  movistar which obviously recognizes that and is
de movistar que obvio reconoce eso y que
grateful to them but that I knew them
se los agradece pero que los conocía
for a long time hendry four
desde hace tiempo a hendry hace cuatro
years ago to perfect delete because
años a perfecto borrar porque
basically it seemed stupid to me that
básicamente me parecía estúpido que las
people criticized him for a
personas pues lo criticaron por una
decision he made to go to another country
decisión que tomó de irse a otro país
to pay less taxes but
para pagar menos impuestos pero
obviously freedom of
obviamente existe la libertad de
expression exists and many people
expresión y muchas personas pues le
thought this was wrong so after this I
pareció mal esto entonces luego de esto
made the video here doesn't it seem
hice el vídeo de aquí no te parece
strange to you that I have not criticized
extraño de que yo no he criticado a
anyone in any of my videos that I have not
nadie en ninguno de mis vídeos que no he
defamed any and that precisely in that
difamado ninguno y que justamente en ese
video comes defamer git simply
vídeo llega difamador git simplemente
because she says so she has no proof she
porque ella lo dice no tiene pruebas no
has no arguments simply because she already
tiene argumentos simplemente porque ya
says so it even has the same title
lo dice incluso tiene el mismo título
basically as the one about rubios in which I do
básicamente que el de rubios en el cual
not criticize him I simply tell the truth
no lo critico simplemente digo la verdad
of the matter after this I did start
del asunto luego de esto sí que comience
uploading videos about the ceo because no
a subir vídeos sobres al ceo ya que sin
matter what I uploaded I would get
importar lo que subiera me llegaba a
hate anyway today here because it
hate de todas maneras hoy aquí porque
avoids the vein of visits in passing
evita el filón de de visita de pasada
100 visits to 20 thousand currently it is
100 visitas a 20 mil actualmente está
returning to receive drawing content
volviendo a recibir contenido de dibujo
as surely many know it was
como ya seguramente muchos saben fue
colo that they start my channel but I
colo que inicien mi canal pero me
find this response from rayita and
encuentro con esta respuesta de rayita y
the truth is that  I was
la verdad que estaba
and all the stuff that had come to me
y toda la cosa que me había llegado por
from her even on my Instagram and
parte de ella incluso en mi instagram y
this time I didn't want to sit idly by,
esta vez no quería quedarme cruzado de
the thing is coming from her I'm
la cosa está llega por parte de ella te
going to apply to you because churra the harassment hasn't
voy a aplicar porque churra el acoso no
come to you from her because it's
te ha llegado por parte de ella porque
true that she well the thing
sí que es verdad que ella bueno la cosa
was that she
fue que ella
gave me she mentioned it in a live stream is that
me dio mencionó en un directo es que
now I'm remembering the media
ahora me voy acordando los medios
mentioned the video in a live stream and also I think I
mencionó en un directo el vídeo y además
remember that she gave some kind of
creo recordar que dio algún tipo de
information that made the
datos que hacía que se identificase el
video identifiable it's not an agreement and she said something about the
vídeo no es un acuerdo y dijo algo del
title or something like that okay and
título o algo por el estilo vale y
then people may get to the
entonces puede que la gente llegar al
video but realize that if she
vídeo pero date cuenta que ella si
had wanted she would have mentioned you directly
hubiera querido te menciona directamente
because just like you can talk about
porque al igual que tú puedes hablar de
her she can beat you and you would have
ella ella te puede vencer a ti y te
loved it if she had
hubiera encantado que ella te hubiera
mentioned you dude you would have loved it
mencionado colega te hubiera encantado
on youtube she mentioned look I
en youtube ha mencionado mira yo
sincerely am not going to finish watching
sinceramente no voy a terminar de ver
this video because it seems like some
este vídeo porque me parece unas
pretty regrettable justifications
justificaciones bastante lamentables
okay and I would do one thing I would do one
vale y yo haría una cosa yo haría una
thing
cosa
I am this guy and I would say look what you're
yo soy este chico y yo diría mira que me
sending me Caribbean
mandas caribe
she herself says that thanks to the
ella misma dice que gracias a los
greats in an interview with
grandes en una entrevista de
Movistar what you're sending me not
de movistar lo que me estás mandando no
health
la salud
in  the 14th minute
en el minuto 14
is silly to deny it you know it's silly to
es tontería negarlo sabes es tontería
deny it but well, he listens to us a little I
negarlo pero bueno nos escucha un poco
understand that they were the ones who at the
entiendo que fueron ellos los que en su
time also
momento también
[Music]
[Música]
director of major
director de mayor
of giving many thanks he doesn't
de dar muchísimas gracias tampoco lo
say it so literally but I understand
dice tan literalmente pero yo mira
the girl's anger
entiendo el enfado de la chica
sincerely so
sinceramente así que
I will tell this guy to
que yo le dirá a este chaval que lo
understand it too and to look at a detail
comprenda también y que mire un detalle
and the detail that she as much as she
y el detalle que ella por mucho que te
told you such did not know how to handle it
haya dicho tal no la sabía gestionar
well she neither I imagine that she
bien ella tampoco no me imagino que no
is not more used to this but I will
estará más acostumbrada a esto pero yo
tell this guy to look at the detail
le diré a este chico que mire el detalle
that she has had that she is not strip
que ha tenido ella de que no está tira
of the video in the end no matter how
del vídeo al final por mucho se ha
upset she has been take it off your guy in a good way
molestado quítalo tu tío de buena forma
with the tube and take it off in a good way
con el tubo y quítalo de buena forma
understand what bothers her and
entiende lo que le molesta a ella y
take it off
quítalo
because in the end the insinuation is ugly not
porque al final es fea la insinuación no
a little no
un poco no
but it is not a defamation either in a
pero no es una difamación tampoco en
reportable way in a big way but
plan denunciable en plan gordo pero
obvious I understand it
obvia la entiendo